igive.com 2011-12-17

# iGive.com - Privacy Policy

**It is possible to utilize iSearchiGive.com without becoming an iGive.com member and without providing us your e-mail address. In that instance, any references to the collection or utilization of e-mail address and other information supplied by a user do not apply.**  

**How do iGive.com and iSearchiGive.com use the information collected?**

We will be utilizing your e-mail address to send you our newsletters and to alert you to special opportunities and offers. If you have given permission, we will also forward newsletters from your cause to you, and will let your cause know that you are supporting the cause with your online shopping.

We will disclose information that we gather only in the aggregate in order to analyze our usage and attract advertisers, corporate sponsors or merchant affiliates. We will take great care and caution to keep whatever information we gather safe.

Our referral program rewards the causes when members refer new shoppers to iGive.com through their personalized Tell-a-Friend links. If you join through such a link, your name is revealed to your referrer only if you give permission during registration. No other information is shared or revealed with the individual who referred you, or with any other party. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and e-mail address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time e-mail inviting him or her to visit the site. iGive.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may [contact us](http://support.igive.com/Main/frmNewTicket.aspx) to request that we remove this information from our database.  

Please note that when a member visits or shops at our advertisers or with an iGive.com merchant or in the iGive.com Mall, they are dealing with another company, not iGive.com. This means that you enter into a relationship with that company / Web site separately from iGive.com. Any information you share with that advertiser or merchant is subject to their policies and practices, not to iGive.com's policies or practices. Members are encouraged to read the privacy policies of our merchant partners.

> Back to top

**What information is collected?**

We track when and how you visit and use our site, either directly or using browser add-ons / extensions like the iGive Toolbar or Button. We track the iGive stores you visit, the search terms you use, and purchase information provided to us by the stores you use via iGive so that we may credit you appropriately.

> Back to top

**What information is NOT collected?**

We do NOT collect or have any access to your credit card information. Stores do not share that information with us, either.

We do NOT collect or have any access to social security numbers. Generally, we do not collect or receive detail on your purchases. In some instances, you or a store will share purchase detail with us, but we do not retain that information.

> Back to top

**What security measures are taken to protect member and other information?**

Non-authorized personnel do not have physical access to our computers or database. Employees review security guidelines on a quarterly basis, as well as any time new policies are added. The servers that we use to store personally identifiable information are kept in a locked room at a secure facility which requires fingerprint authorization for entry.

> Back to top

**Are cookies or tracking pixels used by iGive.com?**

We and certain of our vendors use â€˜cookies' to make visiting our site and visiting iGive.com merchants a better, easier experience. We do link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. This is done to allow us or our vendors to recognize you when you visit iGive.com, iGive.com merchants, and the iGive.com Mall. Cookies also make it easier for us to track your activity and purchases and to match them with your member registration and charity so that you and your selected cause receive the appropriate credit. We do not share this information with others.

Some iGive.com e-mails contain a transparent GIF file, also called a tracking pixel. If you choose to download the images within our e-mails, the tracking pixel will allow us to identify your web browser through a unique cookie, which allows us to know if and when you opened our e-mail. This information allows us to better understand which of our e-mails are resulting in traffic to iGive.com and our merchants. Information gained through pixel tracking is only shared in aggregate; we do not share personally identifiable information gathered through pixel tracking. 

> Back to top

**INSTRUCTIONS FOR MANAGING YOUR SETTINGS AND MEMBERSHIP**

**How can I change my profile and/or preferences (for iGive.com members only)?**

You may review or update any of the personally identifiable information that iGive.com maintains online by visiting "My Settings," which can be found at: [http://www.iGive.com/html/mysettings.cfm](http://www.igive.com/html/mysettings.cfm) (only members can access this page). Directions will be provided on to change your profile and/or preferences. Also, once a year we may send you an e-mail requesting you to update your demographic information to keep your membership current.

As a member, you may opt out of receiving any newsletter or correspondence at any time by following the link provided in each newsletter, or by visiting the "My Settings" area, and clicking the link to Change Your Newsletter Subscriptions. You can also visit the page directly by following this link: [http://www.iGive.com/html/newsprefs.cfm](http://www.igive.com/html/newsprefs.cfm) (only members can access this page) You will need the password you gave when you registered with iGive.com to change your subscriptions.

> Back to top

**What if I wish to resign my membership?**

If you wish to resign your iGive.com membership just go to the "Cancel Membership" section of the iGive.com Web site at [http://www.iGive.com/html/cancel.cfm](http://www.igive.com/html/cancel.cfm) and follow the instructions explaining how to resign your membership.

> Back to top

**How will I be notified of changes to these privacy statements?**

If iGive.com materially changes our practices in handling personally identifiable information, as described in this policy, we will notify you by posting the changes on this privacy statement and on the iGive.com Web site at least 30 days prior to their implementation.

You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change.

> Back to top

**Who can I contact if I have additional questions?**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should [contact us](http://support.igive.com/Main/frmNewTicket.aspx).

iGive.com can also be reached by phone at (800) 372-6095 or by mail at:  
iGive.com Holdings LLC  
Suite 351  
19821 NW 2nd Ave  
Miami Gardens, FL 33169

_This document's last major update was on 5/20/08. Information was added on 7/11/11 explaining about what information is collected and updating contact information. This privacy statement covers the websites: www.iGive.com and www.iSearchiGive.com._

> Back to top
